open drawer
close drawer
take fork
take mug
crack egg
place eggshells on bin
rinse hands
scramble eggs
place fork on sink
take pan
place pan on stove
pour omelette on pan
rinse mug
wash mug
place mug on dryer
open cabinet
place oil on cabinet
take bowl
add water
place bowl on counter
take spoon
mix porridge
take spatula
flip omelette
cook omelette
open fridge
take cheese
close fridge
take knife
take slicing table
slice cheese
add cheese omelette
fold omelette
turn off stove
take cheese
open fridge
put cheese on fridge
close fridge
take plate
put plate on dishwasher
wash plate
rinse plate
dry plate
put towell on stove
take towell
dry
plate
put omelette on plate
take spatula
put plate on counter